inkscape is a large application with
Inkscape是一个大型应用程序，具有
lots of advanced
很多先进的
tools and features as a new user you
作为新用户的工具和功能
have a lot to learn and you're probably
有很多东西要学，你可能会
going to make some mistakes along the
将会犯下一些错误
way
道路
in this video i'll be going over some of
在这段视频中，我将回顾一些
the more common mistakes new users make
新用户犯的错误越多
so you can avoid making them yourself
这样你就可以避免自己动手做了
[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logosbynick.com and in
我是来自logosbynick.com的尼克
this video i'll be going over five of
这段视频我将重温五个
the most common mistakes users make
用户最常犯的错误
when they're new to inkscape and if
当他们是Inkscape新手时，如果
you'd like to learn more about how
您想了解更多有关如何
inkscape works
Inkscape作品
be sure to check out my inkscape master
一定要看看我的Inkscape大师
class it's a collection of over 60
班级它是一个超过60个人的集合
videos where i go over every tool and
我看过每一个工具和
feature in inkscape
Inkscape中的功能
and i explain what it is and demonstrate
我解释了它是什么，并展示了
how it works i'll have a link in the
它是如何工作的，我会在
description of the video if you want to
视频描述(如果您想要
check that out
看看这个
that being said let's get started
话虽如此，让我们开始吧
one of the most common mistakes i see
我看到的最常见的错误之一
new users making is trying to perform
新用户Making正在尝试执行
path operations on objects that aren't
对不是的对象执行路径操作
paths
路径
in short path operations allow you to
在最短路径操作中，您可以
take multiple objects and turn them into
获取多个对象并将其转化为
new objects
新对象
based on how they interact with each
基于它们如何相互作用
other you can unify them
其他的你可以统一他们
subtract them from each other use the
将它们相减，使用
intersecting area to create a new
相交区域以创建新的
object and more however this only works
对象和更多对象，但是这只起作用。
on
在……上面
individual objects that are paths so if
作为路径的单个对象，因此如果
you're trying to unify
你在试图统一
groups of objects for example it's not
例如，对象组不是
going to work
去上班
you'll have to ungroup the objects first
您必须先将对象解组
same for text objects
文本对象也是如此
and rasterized images these objects are
以及这些对象的光栅化图像
not
不
paths therefore the path operations will
路径，因此路径操作将
have no effect on them
对他们没有影响
another mistake you might make if you're
你可能犯的另一个错误，如果你是
new to inkscape and don't know any
Inkscape新手，不认识任何人
better
更好的
is neglecting to respect the power of
是忽视了尊重
the edit paths by nodes tool
按结点编辑路径工具
the nodes tool allows you to transform
结点工具可用于转换
all of the individual coordinate points
所有单独的坐标点
of a vector object
向量对象的
but it also has the power to freeze up
但它也有冻结的力量
the software
该软件
and make it crash if you try to select
并使其崩溃，如果您尝试选择
objects with too many nodes
节点过多的对象
this is more of a problem with inkscape
这更像是Inkscape的问题
than it is with the user so i can't
而不是和用户在一起所以我不能
really blame someone for walking into
真的很责怪某人走进
this problem
这个问题
but it is something you need to be aware
但这是你需要意识到的事情
of regardless when working with the
无论何时使用
nodes tool
节点工具
always be careful not to select objects
始终注意不要选择对象
that are really complex
这真的很复杂
and may have lots of nodes if possible
并且在可能的情况下可能具有许多节点
try to break your objects apart into
试着把你的物体分解成
separate objects first
首先分离对象
another mistake you might make as a new
你可能会犯的另一个新错误
user to inkscape is forgetting to
Inkscape的用户忘记了
delegate
代表
whether or not you want the strokes on
不管你是否想要笔划
your object to scale
您要缩放的对象
with the object every vector object has
有了对象，每个向量对象都有
two properties
两个属性
a fill color and a stroke that acts as
填充颜色和笔触，作为
an outline around your object
对象周围的轮廓
and the stroke has its own size
而且笔划有它自己的大小
independent of the size of the object
与对象的大小无关
if you scale down your object you may
如果您缩小您的对象，您可以
notice that the thickness of the stroke
请注意，笔划的粗细
scales down with it if you'd like to
如果您愿意，可以随其缩小
maintain the thickness of the stroke
保持笔划的粗细
regardless of how you scale your object
无论您如何缩放对象
though you can find the setting for that
不过，你可以找到它的设置
in the tool settings menu for the select
在工具设置菜单中选择
tool just look for the icon that says
工具只需查找显示以下内容的图标
when scaling objects scale the stroke
缩放对象时，缩放笔划
width by the same proportion when you
宽度以相同的比例
hover your cursor over it
将光标悬停在其上
if you'd like your strokes to scale
如果你想让你的笔划变得有度
alongside your objects
在你的物品旁边
leave it enabled if you'd like to
如果您愿意，请将其保持启用状态
maintain a fixed size for your strokes
保持笔划的固定大小
regardless of scaling
不考虑扩展
simply turn it off
只要关掉它就行了
next up on our list of common mistakes
接下来是我们的常见错误清单
you might make as a new inkscape user is
作为Inkscape的新用户，您可能会
forgetting to disable snapping when
在以下情况下忘记禁用捕捉
you're working
你在工作
snapping is a really useful feature that
捕捉是一项非常有用的功能，
allows you to draw with precision
使您可以精确地绘制
for example let's say you have two boxes
例如，假设您有两个盒子
and you want to place them
你想把它们放在
flush against each other doing this
在做这件事时彼此脸红
freehands would prove difficult because
徒手会被证明是困难的，因为
it would be nearly impossible for you to
你几乎不可能
know
知
exactly where the edges are with
边缘的确切位置
snapping enabled though
但已启用捕捉
your objects will snap directly against
您的对象将直接对齐
each other once they're in close
一旦他们靠近，就会彼此靠近
proximity
邻近性
as useful as this may be there will be
尽管这可能很有用，但还是会有
some instances where you're trying to
在某些情况下，您试图
create something
创造一些东西
but the snaps keep getting in the way
但这些照片一直挡在路上
and drawing your cursor away from where
并将您的光标从
you actually want it to be
你真的想让它成为
to disable snapping just click the
要禁用捕捉，只需单击
enable snapping icon
启用捕捉图标
in the top left portion of your screen
在屏幕的左上角
or what i like to do is just press
或者我喜欢做的就是按下
shift and 5 on the keyboard as a
键盘上的Shift和5作为
shortcut
捷径
the final common mistake new inkscape
最后一个常见错误新Inkscape
users make has to do with exporting png
用户制作与输出PNG有关
images
图像
exporting allows you to generate usable
导出允许您生成可用的
copies of your designs in the dot png
在点PNG中复制您的设计
format
格式
this is useful for exporting your logo
这对于导出您的徽标很有用
for use on a website
在网站上使用
generating app icons graphics for a game
为游戏生成应用程序图标图形
so on and so forth
以此类推
one aspect of the export menu that many
出口菜单的一个方面是
users overlook though
然而，用户忽略了
is the export area section this is what
是出口区吗？这是什么
allows you to dictate
允许您口述
exactly what gets exported the page
页面到底导出了什么内容
option will export everything inside of
选项将导出中的所有内容
your page border
您的页面边框
the drawing option will export
绘制选项将导出
everything inside and outside of your
你的身体内外的一切
page border
页面边框
the selection option will only export an
选择选项将仅导出一个
object you have selected
您已选择的对象
and the custom option allows you to
自定义选项允许您
manually define coordinate points
手动定义坐标点
on the x and y axis of your canvas that
在画布的x轴和y轴上
you'd like to export
你想出口吗？
where a lot of users run into trouble is
很多用户遇到麻烦的地方是
when they think they're exporting one
当他们认为他们正在出口一个
thing
一件事
but they're really exporting something
但他们实际上是在出口一些东西
else because the proper export area
否则是因为适当的出口地区
setting hasn't been selected
尚未选择设置
this is why it's important to always pay
这就是为什么总是付钱很重要的原因
close attention to the settings
密切关注设置
in the export menu and that should do it
在EXPORT菜单中，应该可以这样做
for today's video
今天的视频
hopefully these pointers will make your
希望这些指点能让你的
learning experience a little easier
学习体验更容易一点
if you have any questions or need
如果您有任何问题或需要
clarification on anything i've gone over
澄清我所说过的一切
in this video
在此视频中
just leave a comment below and as always
只需在下面留下评论，一如既往
thanks for watching
感谢收看
[Music]
[音乐]